SYNCHRONIZATION-SUBTITLES
VASILISIF!!!!!
There's a hundred thousand streets
in the city.
You don't need to know the route.
You give me a time and a place,
I give you a five minute window.
Anything happens in that five
minutes and I'm yours.
No matter what.
Anything happens a minute either side
of that and you are on your own.
Do you understand?
Good.
And you won't be able to reach me
on this phone again.
Hey, there you are!
She's down there.
Plain Jane boring,
just like you asked for,
but I dropped in 300 horses
on the inside, she is gonna fly!
You look like a zombie kid.
You getting any sleep?
Can I offer you some Benzedrine,
Dexedrine, caffeine, nicotine?
Oh you don't smoke, that's right.
Better off.
There she is!
"Chevy Impala". The most popular car
in the state of California.
No one will be looking at you.
...Robert Victor 3.
License 5-1-4, Robert Victor 3...
Code 30 Ringer located
at 421 South Alameda.
Reports of shots fired at Code 30.
Come on!
Where the fuck is he? Come on!
Unit 5, what's your 20?
We are approximately two minutes
from that location.
Come on, man! Where the hell are you?
Come on!
Come on! Get in! Get in! Get in!
Go, go, go, go, go!
All unit be advised,
possible vehicle in question;
Late model, silver impala.
1-Adam-3, South Bay at Seventh, clear.
Roger, 1-Adam-3.
Requesting air unit support.
Unit 5 to dispatch,
heading eastbound on Sixth.
Copy that, Unit 5.
Base to Air 3.
Any sign of that silver impala?
Air 3 to Base. Negative.
Got a visual, heading west on
Seventh Street bridge.
Copy, Air 3. All units, be advised...
Base, Air 3 here. We've lost visual
on suspect.
Base to Air 3. Possible gang shooting
in progress.
Proceed immediately
to Washington and La Brea.
Roger, dispatch. I'm out.
All westbound units be advised.
Suspect last seen near
Seventh Street and Santa Fe.
Dispatch, this is 1-Adam-6.
Possible suspect vehicle,
sighted at stoplight.
Stand by.
Roger, Unit 6.
~ I'm giving you a night call ~
~ tell you how I feel ~
~ I want to drive you through the night ~
~ down the hills ~
~ I'm gonna tell you something ~
~ you don't want to hear ~
~ I'm gonna show you where it's dark ~
~ but have no fear ~
~ There's something inside you ~
~ it's hard to explain ~
~ They're talking about you, boy ~
~ but you're still the same ~
~ There's something inside you ~
~ it's hard to explain ~
~ They're talking about you, boy ~
~ but you're still the same ~
~ There's something inside you ~
~ it's hard to explain ~
~ They're talking about you, boy ~
~ but you're still the same ~
- What floor?
- Fourth. Thanks.
Hey, kid...
you know what?
Director wants to see a rollover.
Are you okay with that?
Remember, if you don't feel good,
just abort the shot.
There's no shame in that, all right?
I mean, you're... You're doubling
for the star.
You' re not like a day player
or anything.
And I got you $500 more. Huh?
Of course we split that.
You okay? Ready to go?
All right, I'm counting on you.
Excuse me, pal. I just
need a minute here.
You see, before I put you on camera,
I need you to sign this... contract.
It just basically releases liability
to the company
in case you die, get maimed,
or seriously injured.
And... action!
All right, that's a cut!
Oh Kid! That was fantastic.
Just fantastic!
Okay, how you doing? You all right?
You were good. You were good.
That was perfect...
- You're a monkey!
- No, you're the monkey!
- You're the monkey!
You're a monkey!
Hey, tell me one thing.
- I love you.
Ah!
- Where should I put these?
- In the kitchen. Thank you.
Just be a second.
Scary.
Hey, you want a toothpick?
You want a glass of water?
Okay.
Thanks.
So, did you just moved to L.A?
No, I've been here for a while.
- You are just new here?
- Mmm-hmm.
That's Benicio's father.
Where is he?
He's in prison.
Oh.
What do you do?
I drive.
Like a limo driver?
- No, like for movies.
- Oh.
Doing all the car chases and stuff?
Yeah.
Isn't that dangerous?
It's only part time.
Mostly I work at the garage.
- Where?
- Receda Boulevard.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Thanks for the water.
- Say bye.
- Bye.
Mr. Rose, your food sir. Okay.
Chicken chow mein and...
some peking duck.
Where are the chopsticks?
- Oh, you know. The guy just...
- Go get them. Go get them.
I don't want that. I don't want that.
You eat it.
Chopsticks and a fortune cookie.
Put out the fucking cigarette,
I'm eating!
I'm sorry.
What's the matter with you?
I'm just... What happened to all the
ashtrays in this town?
You run a perfectly good business.
I don't know, why you wanna change that now.
You know how much
my business made last year?
Thirty grand.
I can build a car in six months
and in six seconds these jerks
write it off as a stunt
that won't even make it to the movie.
See, all I need is a hard used stock car.
That's all.
And I figure we start off small
town circuit; we work our way up.
Once we get to the show,
we're talking millions.
- I have the chopsticks, sir.
- Yeah. Where's the cookies?
- Uh... You know, I...
- Forget it. Forget it.
So, you still haven't given me a number.
All right...
430,000 dollars.
Oh...!
Mr.Rose, I wouldn't come to you with this,
unless I was absolutely sure about it!
How can you be sure, Shannon?
What do you got that the big
professional race teams don't?
I got the driver.
You just told me they had
half a dozen drivers.
Not like this one.
This kid is special.
I've been working with him for a while.
I've never seen anything like it.
If I had the money, I'd back him myself.
Yeah, but you don't have the money.
Mr.Rose, you put this kid behind
the wheel...
there's nothing he can't do.
There's money here. You can't lose.
Fuck you eating chink food in
my fucking restaurant?
What's a Jew doing running a pizzeria?
You remember Shannon.
Take a fucking hike. I want to talk
to my partner.
Hah, I'm just fucking with you.
How you doing Shannon?
How's the fucking leg?
I've paid my debt.
I'll think about it. Okay?
But I wanna meet the kid first.
That's all I ask.
Come on, I want you to meet somebody.
Whatever you do like about the car,
don't say anything.
I want to drive the price down a little bit.
Kid, I want you to meet Mr.Bernie Rose.
Nice to meet you.
My hands are a little dirty.
So are mine.
Good driving out there.
Thanks.
He's a good kid.
So? What do you think?
Do we get the 400?
I'll give you 300 for 70 percent.
Done!
Right. Good.
You won't be sorry!
- I'm Shannon.
- Hi. Irene.
- Irene. How can I help you?
- Uh... It just broke down.
- Just broke down. Just like that.
- Mmm-hmm.
You want me to take a look at it?
All right. Uh...
We got all our bays full.
Um, hey pal, just drop it down here.
We'll push it in all right?
We wanna... push her into number three.
- The car. Not you.
- Oh good.
- Hi.
- Uhh...You two know each other?
- Don't!
Ohh... look at that.
- We're neighbors.
- Neighbors, very good.
Well, we'll try to be neighborly too.
You blinked!
What?
- Can I call a cab from here?
- Yeah, sure.
What am I talking about?
You and the kid are neighbors, right?
He can take you home.
Oh no. I'd feel bad.
Oh, no...Don't even think twice about it.
He'd be happy to do it.
He's a good guy.
You know, he walked into my shop here
about five or six years ago...
right out of the blue, asking for a job.
So, I put him to the test,
see what he could do.
The kid's amazing.
So, I hired him on the spot.
Boom!
At about half the wages i normally pay.
He didn't even blink an eye.
Hey kid, come over here for a second,
will you?
And I have been exploiting him ever since.
Shhhh...Don't tell him!
It looks like we have a bigger problem
than I thought.
And we're gonna have to keep
the car here for a few days.
So, I offered your services to take,
Benicio and Irene home.
That be okay?
- Yeah sure.
- Yeah.
I don't have wheels... on my car.
- Okay.
- It's one think you should know about me.
- Well, put the tyres on.
- You got five minutes?
Yeah.
Hey, do you wanna see something?
Okay.
~ Back against the wall and odds ~
~ with the strength of a will and a cause ~
~ your pursuits are called outstanding ~
~ you're emotionally complex ~
~ Against the grain of dystopic claims ~
~ on the thoughts your actions entertained ~
~ and you have proved to be ~
~ A real human being ~
~ and a real hero ~
~ Real human being ~
~ A pilot on a cold, cold morn' ~
~ one-hundred fifty-five people on board ~
~ all safe and all rescued ~
~ from the slowly sinking ship ~
~ Water warmer than his head so cool ~
~ in that tight bind knew what to do ~
~ and you have proved to be ~
~ A real human being ~
~ real human being ~
That was good.
He had a good time.
Me too.
Sorry, if I put you on the spot
showing up like that.
It's okay.
I'm not doing anything this weekend.
If you want a ride or something.
Don't worry about her bumps and
bruises, that's just fiberglass.
That's easily replaceable.
Put a... coat of paint on there,
some sponsors decals.
Look at the tread on the tyre,
is still good huh?
We're in business!
We paid 300 fucking grand
for this piece of shit?
I paid for it. Out of my own pocket.
This is just the shell.
It's the inside that counts.
Not the outside.
- Right, Shannon?
- You are correct sir.
Fuck that shit. I pay 300 for something,
I want everybody to fucking see it.
Of course you do!
Now this!
That is one motherfucking fine-ass
pussy mobile, motherfucker!
Damn!
Shannon, sell him the car.
He wouldn't be able to find pussy
in a whorehouse.
You know what? This car will even
make you good-looking.
I'm already good-looking, pal.
How's it going?
When's our first race?
Uh, pretty soon.
You gonna be ready?
I hope so.
Huh..."I hope so".
Hey, no false modesty.
I got a lot of money in this.
Did Shannon ever tell you how we met?
No.
I used to produce movies.
In the 80's.
Kind of like action films. Sexy stuff.
One critic called them "European".
I thought they were shit.
Anyway he arranged all the cars for me.
Did all the stunts.
I liked him. I liked having him around.
Even though, he overcharged
the shit out of me.
His next business venture,
he got involved with some of Nino's friends.
They didn't go for the overcharging bit.
They broke his pelvis.
He's never had a lot of luck.
The reason I'm telling you this is,
is that he has a lot invested in you.
And so do I.
So anything you need you call me.
We're a team now.
Huh, I'm excited.
Nino, get the fuck out of here.
- Is he a bad guy?
- Yeah.
How can you tell?
Because... he's a shark.
There's no good sharks?
No... I mean, just look at him.
Does he look like a good guy to you?
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Good.
This is Cindy.
Hi.
That was my husband's lawyer.
He's coming home in a week.
~ I don't eat ~
~ I don't sleep ~
~ I do nothing but think of you ~
~ I don't eat ~
~ I don't sleep ~
~ I do nothing but think of you ~
~ You keep me under your spell ~
You know, we're here celebrating,
but it's, it's a shameful thing...
...what I did.
And...I have a lot of making up to do,
to everyone.
But second chances are rare.
Right?
And that's worth celebrating.
So, I want to make a toast...
...to that lady right there.
Thanks for staying.
I love you, Renie.
Salud.
~ I don't sleep ~
~ I do nothing but think of you ~
~ I don't eat ~
~ I don't sleep ~
~ I do nothing but think of you ~
~ You keep me under your spell ~
Hey.
Hi.
Sorry about the noise.
I was gonna call the cops.
I wish you would.
Oye, getting heavier.
- Hey.
Hey.
How you doing?
- Hi.
- This guy's been telling me a lot about you.
He says, you've been coming around,
helping out a lot.
Yeah? Helping out?
Is that right?
- Is that right?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
That's very nice. That's nice of you.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
You drive for the movies?
Yeah.
- I can take that.
- No, no. I got it. I got it.
Let mommy talk to her friend.
Come on.
Have a good night.
You're Shannon's buddy, right?
We met last year.
You drove me and my brother back
from Palm Springs.
We hired another wheelman.
I spent six months in jail.
My brother, he got himself killed.
I have this sweet job coming up now...
How about this?
You shut you mouth.
Or I'll kick your teeth down
your throat and I'll shut it for you.
Nice seeing you again.
Come on, it's okay.
Come here.
Don't be scared.
Look...
...don't tell mommy, okay?
Okay? It's a secret between the boys.
Oh, fuck me.
Who were they?
What the fuck are you gonna do?
You're gonna go beat them up for me?
Huh, stunt guy?
Why the fuck do you wanna know
who they are?
Huh?
They're some guys that want me
to do a job for them,
and I'm not gonna do it.
That's who they are.
What's the job?
They want me to rob a pawnshop
in the valley.
Why?
Cause I owe them some protection
money, from when I was inside.
It's 2,000 bucks.
But as soon as I got out,
oh, it's 5,000 bucks.
Oh, no, actually, it's 10,000 dollars
20,000 dollars.
Tomorrow I don't know what the fuck
it's gonna be.
What are you gonna do?
That's a very good question.
They said they were gonna come after
Benicio and Irene next.
You okay?
You want something to drink?
What is this you got there?
Can I see?
One of those men gave you that?
Mmm-hmm.
He told me not to lose it.
You want me to keep that for you?
Okay.
How's Benice?
Good.
You just saying that?
No.
What do you mean?
I saw that Standard...
...was in an accident.
Yeah.
What happened?
He got beat up.
Mmm-hmm.
Why?
Just drunk kids.
You should come over.
You should come and see him.
You wanna...you wanna hear a story?
You wanna hear how mommy and me met?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
We were at a party,
and she was 19 years old.
Seventeen!
- You weren't 17.
- I was.
- Wow, so it's illegal.
- Yeah.
All right, so I illegally walked over
to a 17-year-old girl.
I walk up and I say....
..."Hello Miss".
"What is your name?"
And she don't say anything.
And then I said...
"Well, my name is Standard Gabriel."
Then what did you say?
I said...
"Where's the deluxe version?"
She's good, man.
Sharp!
Oh man, it killed me.
And then a year later,
you popped out, man.
It was the best day of my life.
If I drive for you, you get your money.
You tell me where we start, where we're
going, where we're going afterwards.
I give you five minutes
when we get there.
Anything happens in that five minutes
and I'm yours, no matter what.
Anything a minute on either side
of that and you're on your own.
I don't sit in while you're
running it down,
I don't carry a gun,
I drive.
You look like you're hard to work with.
Not if we understand each other.
What's to understand?
I can't do this thing alone.
You got Blanche.
Come on man.
She's beautiful. Look at her.
What the fuck you rolling your eyes at for?
You know, get the fuck out of here.
Get up!
Standard, take her with you,
and go get her a fucking coke!
Okay, here's the deal.
This much for Blanche,
this much for that asshole,
minus what he owes me,
and this much for you.
You're still interested?
Good! Anything else?
When you get your money, his debt's paid.
He's out for good.
And you never go near his family again.
Do you understand?
I'm here with my family.
And my new friend.
And...
...toast to the future.
To our future.
Hey.
I'll see you in 5 minutes.
See you in 4.
Oh, my God!
Shit!
How much did Cook say, we will be get?
Fourty grand.
Stay here.
When was the last time
you saw your husband?
Can you answer the question?
Ma'am.
Hello?
Benicio, is that you?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hi...
Your mother there?
Uh... She's sitting down
talking to the police.
Okay, just tell her I'm gonna
call her back. Okay?
Okay, bye.
In related news, an attempted robbery
turned tragic today,
when the owner of a local pawnshop
opened fire on an intruder.
The armed robber was pronounced
dead at the scene.
He has been identified as Standard Gabriel
of Echo Park, Los Angeles.
Other details are unclear,
but the owner of the pawnshop
told reporters that
Gabriel acted alone
and that no money had been stolen.
In other news, four high school
athletes were arrested...
If he saw you take the money...
...and he saw you get in the car...
...then why didn't he say anything?
I've no idea.
Did you have any idea
there'd be a second car?
I already told you everything.
Now, you've just got a little
boy's father killed.
And you almost got us killed.
And now you're lying to me.
So how about this?
From now on, every word
out of your mouth is the truth.
Or I'm gonna hurt you.
Do you understand?
Now, what did Cook tell you?
He said there'd be another car
to hold us up,
but he didn't say anything about
all this money,
he didn't say anything about anyone
getting killed.
You were gonna rip us off?
What's his real name?
He says it's Chris,
but I just call him Cook.
You're gonna take me to him...
right now.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Easy, easy!
What did you do with the cash?
Cause I could keep it safe for you
if you wa...
Will you stop?
This guy Cook...have a real name?
Chris.
Maybe.
I'll ask Bernie...
see if he knows him.
Jesus, I can't...
I can't stop thinking about what
we could do with all that dough.
- Would you stop?
- All right!
You know, a lot of guys messing around
with married women,
but you're the only one I know who..
who robs a joint
just to pay back the husband.
Crazy!
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Where's Cook?
He's in the dressing room.
Where's that?
It's over there.
Whose money do I have?
Don't worry, they're gonna
come get it.
No! No!
Call them.
Somebody call Nino!
Do you remember this?
Hello?
Nino?
No, sorry pal. Why don't you call
back later? We're closed.
I could, but I think Nino would be upset
that you made him wait.
Can I ask what this is about?
I have something of his.
And that would be?
A million dollars.
Please hold.
You have something
fucking belongs to me?
Seems that way.
And you're calling me...
...why?
You expect me to buy my own shit
back from you?
I'm not selling it.
I'm gonna give you a time and a place,
and you're gonna come and get it.
Do you understand?
And what do you get out of it?
Just that.
Out of it.
And your partners are happy with that?
I don't have any partners.
You discuss this with... anybody else?
No, just you.
You're not very good at this, are you?
Go check out who this fucking guy is.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Can't talk, I have to go.
Can I just walk with you for a...
Yeah.
I have to tell you something.
Standard was into some...
...guys in prison for a lot of money.
And they were gonna hurt you and
Benicio if he didn't pay it.
He asked me for my help.
Everything went wrong, you know.
I'm sorry.
I still got the money.
You can have it, if you wanted to.
You can take Benicio and...
I just thought you could get out
of here, if you wanted.
I could come with you.
I could look out for you.
Sorry, uh...
...wrong floor.
They came to my apartment, Shannon.
How'd they know where I live?
I told you, I was gonna call Bernie.
I just wanted him know that...
that it wasn't about...
That you're not interested in the money,
that you just did it for the girl.
- What the fuck did you just say?
- No, no!
- I just...
- Why did you have to fucking tell them about Irene?
- Calm down!
- You told them about Irene!
Calm down, kid. Just calm down.
I should fucking kill you!
You told them about Irene!
I just...I just wanted him to know...
...that as soon as you return the money,
that was the end of it.
That's all. I didn't know...
How was I supposed to know?
How was I supposed to know that? Okay?
Look, let me, let me just talk to Bernie.
Okay?
Why you got to fuck everything up, Shannon?
How was I supposed to know,
everything led to Nino?
They're gonna come looking for me.
And they're gonna come for you.
Do you understand?
You gotta get out of here.
And you gotta get out now.
- Listen to me.
- Oh, God.
Listen to me, Shannon.
Listen.
You get out of here and you never
fucking come back.
You never come back.
What are you gonna do?
I already gave you my advice!
You should have taken the money
and left the guy alone.
It's not that simple Bernie.
No, of course not! Now that it's
bounced up in your face!
You know, I owe you this guy. Just give me
a little time and I'll get rid of him.
Shut the fuck up.
You fucking monkey!
The money.. belongs to some half-assed
wise guy out of Philly.
Now, I got tipped off...
...he was stashing a million bucks
in a pawnshop.
He was gonna invest it here in L.A.
He was gonna set up a rival operation.
So, you stole from the East Coast mob?
No, I stole from some jumped-up punk
who was trying to step on our action.
Yeah? Then why didn't you come to me,
before you set up this dummy robbery?
Before you hire this piece of shit.
This is something off to the side, Bernie.
I didn't wanna involve you in this.
Well, I'm involved now!
Let me tell you something.
Anybody...
...anybody, finds out you stole
from the Family,
we're both dead.
What fucking Family?
The Family who still calls me
a fucking kike?
To my face?
Yeah, I'm 59 years old Bernie.
They still pinch my cheek
like I'm some fucking kid.
Family...
The money always flows up, Izzy.
You know that.
That's why this driver's gotta go, Bernie.
He's gotta go.
And your pal, Shannon. I mean these
are the only two guys who can...
...tie me to this robbery.
Now it's your turn to clean up after me.
All these priceless cars...
One would think you'd have better locks.
Why?
Door is always open to you.
Going somewhere?
Uh...
Thinking about it.
I'm looking for your driver.
You break in here,
I figure it's bad news.
No, Shannon.
It's bad luck.
2,000 heists a year in this city,
he has to pick the wrong one.
He tried to put it right.
Well, he picked the wrong guy for that too.
My partner is a belligerent asshole,
with his back against the wall.
Right now, so am I.
If I don't set this straight,
I'm in big trouble.
Any idea where he might be?
Mexico.
Or maybe it was Belize.
Really?
I was getting excited
about this whole thing.
My name on a car!
I mean, look how beautiful.
I wanted to see my name on this thing.
I think we would have made a go
with this business.
Don't worry. Don't worry, that's it!
It's done!
There's no pain, it's over. It's over!
~ Oh, my love ~
~ look and see ~
~ the sun rising from the river ~
~ nature's miracle once more ~
~ will light the world ~
~ But this light ~
~ is not for those men ~
~ still lost in ~
~ an old black shadow ~
~ Won't you help me to believe ~
~ that they will see ~
~ a day ~
~ A brighter day ~
~ when all the shadows ~
~ will fade away ~
~ that day I'll cry ~
~ that I believe ~
~ Oh, my love ~
~ high above us ~
~ the sun now ~
~ embraces nature ~
~ And from nature we should learn ~
~ that all can start again ~
~ as the stars must fade away ~
~ to give a bright new day ~
What the fuck was that?
Let's get out of here.
Yeah.
Hello?
You know the story about the
scorpion and the frog?
Your friend Nino didn't make it
across the river.
I think this is gone on long enough.
You see any reason for it to continue?
What do you say we meet?
Why?
Well...
...you, me and your girlfriend
are the only players left.
How's that for a reason?
When?
Tomorrow.
There's a place on Sherman Way,
it's a restaurant called "The Great Wall".
You know it?
Can I talk to you?
I won't keep you long.
I have to go somewhere and
I don't think I can come back.
But I just want you to know.
Getting to be around you and Benicio
was the best thing that ever
happened to me.
Did you bring the money?
Here's what I'm prepared to offer.
You give me the money, the girl is safe.
Forever. Nobody knows about her.
She's off the map.
I can't offer you the same.
So, this is what I would suggest.
We conclude our deal,
we'll shake hands.
You.. start the rest of your life.
Any dreams you have, or plans,
or hopes for your future...
...I think you're gonna have
to put that on hold.
For the rest of your life, you're gonna
be looking over your shoulder.
I'm just telling you this because...
...I want you to know the truth.
But the girl is safe.
Where's the money now?
It's in the car.
Come on.
~ Real human being ~
~ A pilot on a cold, cold morn' ~
~ one-hundred fifty-five people on board ~
~ all safe and all rescued ~
~ from the slowly sinking ship ~
~ Water warmer than his head so cool ~
~ in that tight bind knew what to do ~
~ and you have proved to be ~
~ A real human being ~
~ and a real hero ~
~ Real human being ~
EDITING SUBTITLES- VASILISIF!!!!!!!